https://www.bigleaguelawns.com/privacy-policy.html

Shop By Brand
Ariens Cub Cadet Honda SCAG Country Clipper Kubota Bad Boy Dixie Chopper Husqvarna Spartan Simplicity Craftsman Lawnboy Bob Cat ExMark Hustler Snapper Grasshopper Troy Bilt Bradley Ferris John Deere Toro Gravely Wright
Shop By Mower Type
Zero Turn Mowers Stand on Mowers Commercial Walk Behind Tractors Rear Engine Riders WAW Mowers Push Mowers
Hardware How It Works Resellers Contact Us Merchandise
Hours M-F 8:30 AM-5:00 PM EST
+1 (800) 411-0150
Follow Us
Useful Links
Videos
Straighter Stripes
Slideshow
Clean Cut Lawn Care
Mower Attachment
Installation Guide [PDF]
Attachment Details
Zero-Turn Radius Mowers
Commercial Walk-Behind
Lawn & Garden Tractors
Other Information
Mower Overlap
Striping Zones
Athletic Fields
Helpful Info
We can help you along the way.
Give us a call or email.
sales@bigleaguelawns.com
800-411-0150
Fall Hours M-F 8:30 am - 4:30 pm EST
Privacy Policy This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.bigleaguelawn.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing: We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information: You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you. Have us delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Updates to Privacy Policy We may make updates to this Privacy Policy periodically without notification. Please refer to this policy when necessary to check for updates. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-411-0150 or via email at sales@bigleaguelawns.com
We're committed - Let us Help! If you are interested in receiving a sizing recommendation, along with complete pricing, please provide us with as much information as possible. We will get back with you very shortly. Please provide a quotation on the following mower:
Commercial Walk Behind/Stand On Unit
20-22" Walk Behind Mowers
30-33" Walk Behind Mowers (e.g. Toro TimeMaster™)
Please provide your mower brand:
Model # or Series:
Size of your mower deck:
Mower is used for: * My own residence Commercial use
What is your Zip Code? *
Your Email Address [Confirm Spelling]: *
Submit
